<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><copyright>© Jason Sandidge 2023</copyright><description>BSU MET Portfolio</description><language>en</language><link>http://example.org/</link><title>BSU MET Portfolio</title><item><description><![CDATA[<p>At the very beginning of the program, we were tasked with authoring an annotated bibliography on a topic of our choice. I was immediately drawn to the topic of Computational Thinking and how the approach can be applied to aid learning. This artifact focuses on the near, far, and overall transfer effects of instruction in computational thinking. In other words, it focused on studies that examined if instruction in computational thinking positively impacts topics beyond computer science and mathematics.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1U2HyYsYTY7eb28vTAdtznHlBNYLMhdQYWRCTIQdLfqQ/edit?usp=sharing">Computational Thinking Annotated Bibliography</a></strong></p>
]]></description><guid>http://example.org/plo/pedagogy-theory/annotatedbibliography/</guid><link>http://example.org/plo/pedagogy-theory/annotatedbibliography/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><title>Computational Thinking Annotated Bibliography</title></item><item><description><![CDATA[<p>The animation in this artifact lacks sophistication but illustrates a common ethical challenge in my former job as an IT administrator at a small charter school.  Greater autonomy is a wonderful feature of charter schools but that autonomy should not be used to compromise ethical standards or violate school policy.  In this animation, I examine how the temptation to violate technology purchasing policies for friends at work can quickly lead to ethics violations.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.powtoon.com/ws/b4wJVQnKWiY/1/m">Professional Ethics Animation</a></strong></p>
]]></description><guid>http://example.org/plo/ethics/ethicsanimation/</guid><link>http://example.org/plo/ethics/ethicsanimation/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><title>Professional Ethics Animation</title></item><item><description><![CDATA[<p>Real leadership demands ultimate responsibility.  This artifact was developed to leverage technology to help school leaders ensure their online presence meets all applicable legal requirements.  This can be a complicated task, especially in a small charter school setting with limited resources and expertise.  This self-assessment to be completed by school or IT administrators identified all essential components of a website including legal disclosures and policies at the time it was published.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://forms.gle/Qrwpzt3UNqfWpc7x7">School District Website Legal Compliance Self Assessment</a></strong></p>
]]></description><guid>http://example.org/plo/leadership/legalcompliance/</guid><link>http://example.org/plo/leadership/legalcompliance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><title>School District Website Legal Compliance Self Assessment</title></item><item><description><![CDATA[<p>This artifact represents my first foray into the formal evaluation and assessment process.  Although it is anonymized it is a very real evaluation of the school where I was working at the time. The structure provided by the survey enabled a thorough and effective evaluation of the technology processes employed at the school and due to my position there, I was able to effect real change based on the conclusions of this summary.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1uZkXtqmyRH8r4yxFG0b1oEY8pcCk7ABr9c8lKzhBO6M/edit?usp=sharing">School Technology Maturity Benchmarks Evaluation</a></strong></p>
]]></description><guid>http://example.org/plo/evaluation-assessment/techmaturitybenchmarks/</guid><link>http://example.org/plo/evaluation-assessment/techmaturitybenchmarks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><title>School Technology Maturity Benchmarks Evaluation</title></item><item><description><![CDATA[


























<div class="paige-gallery">
    
<div class="align-items-center column-gap-3 d-flex flex-wrap justify-content-center row-gap-3">
            
                


















































    













    



    






<span class="paige-image">















<img  alt="GitLab Logo"   crossorigin="anonymous"    referrerpolicy="no-referrer"  src="/gitlab.png"    title="GitLab Logo"  >
</span>
            
</div>
    
</div>

<p>In the instructional design course (EDTECH 503), I developed an introduction to the installation, configuration, and basic use of a collaborative software engineering tool called git.  This was very applicable personally as I was struggling with the use of the tool in my new position as a test engineer. This section of the completed ID project provided a hypothetical trainer at the company I work at with the rationale of the proposed intervention as well as tables that articulate the learning objectives and activities. The development portion of the artifact provides learning materials as well as guidelines for the assessments to be completed by the learners. Finally, the implementation section provides a detailed description of how to deliver the intervention to new test engineers.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://docs.google.com/document/d/1geEyJJ6x1ZzrlwheV1-ERhZkKGMe6vqO1KN8dtemzK0/edit?usp=sharing">The design and development portion of Team Coding with Git and GitLab</a></strong></p>
]]></description><guid>http://example.org/plo/design-development/git/</guid><link>http://example.org/plo/design-development/git/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><title>Team Coding w/ Git and GitLab</title></item><item><description>Search my portfolio site.</description><guid>http://example.org/search/</guid><link>http://example.org/search/</link><title>Search</title></item></channel></rss>